<resources>
    <string name="app_name">suhide</string>
    <string name="main_title">suhide-lite</string>
    <string name="set_state_root">Root allowed for %s</string>
    <string name="set_state_no_root">Root hidden from %s</string>
    <string name="set_state_hidden">Hiding %s from other apps</string>
    <string name="startup_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="startup_getting_root">Acquiring root access…</string>
    <string name="startup_detecting_root_state">Detecting root state…</string>
    <string name="startup_reading_config">Reading suhide configuration…</string>
    <string name="startup_detecting_apps">Detecting apps…</string>
    <string name="startup_complete">Complete!</string>
    <string name="error_no_root">Could not acquire root access!</string>
    <string name="error_no_supersu">Root is not SuperSU!</string>
    <string name="error_no_sbin_bind">SuperSU is not running in SBIN mode!</string>
    <string name="error_no_suhide">Could not find suhide binaries!</string>
    <string name="btn_kill">Kill</string>
    <string name="kill_title">Killing…</string>
    <string name="kill_message">Terminating all running processes that should not be able to see root, please wait…</string>

    <string name="about"><![CDATA[
        <b>suhide vX.YY</b><br />
        Copyright &copy; 2016-2017 Chainfire &amp; CCMT<br />
        <br />
        <b>Basic operation</b><br />
        You can configure each app if it should be able to see root (green
        icon), if root should be hidden from it (red icon), or if the app
        should be hidden from other apps (blue icon).<br />
        <br />
        For performance reasons it is best to allow apps to have root (green
        icon) by default.<br />
        <br />
        <b>Killing apps</b><br />
        Hiding root from an app only goes into effect the next time the app
        is started. This user interface does not kill apps automatically when
        you select them, because it is a slow operation. The cross icon in the
        app\'s toolbar allows you to manually kill all running instances of apps
        that root should be hidden from, once you are done configuring.<br />
        <br />
        <b>Hiding apps</b><br />
        Some apps (such as games) detect the presence of other apps (such
        as SuperSU). By pressing <b>volume up, volume down, volume up,
        volume down, volume up, volume down</b> (so three times alternated
        volume up, volume down) in less than <b>3 seconds</b>, the selected
        apps will be hidden or unhidden from all other apps (including the
        launcher). In this hidden state, SuperSU will keep granting root to
        already configured apps, and will deny root from all other apps.
    ]]></string>
</resources>
